{
    "subject": "resource/Sweeney_Todd:_The_Demon_Barber_of_Fleet_Street_(1936_film)",
    "predicate": "ontology/writer",
    "object": "resource/H._F._Maltby",
    "human_readable": "H. F. Maltby wrote Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street (1936 film).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9847080707550049,
            "question": "Who wrote the screenplay for the 1936 film 'Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8835394382476807,
            "question": "Is 'Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street' a novel, play, or film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8157806396484375,
            "question": "What was the year of release for the film adaptation of 'Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7958856225013733,
            "question": "What is the title of the screenplay written by H. F. Maltby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5279297828674316,
            "question": "Besides writing screenplays, what other creative pursuits might H. F. Maltby have been involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4656229317188263,
            "question": "What type of work did H. F. Maltby create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4205731749534607,
            "question": "Name a well-known musical composer who might have been involved in creating music for a production of 'Sweeney Todd'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3580739200115204,
            "question": "How did the success of the film influence later adaptations or interpretations of 'Sweeney Todd'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23361967504024506,
            "question": "What elements contribute to the dark and suspenseful nature of 'Sweeney Todd'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2026827335357666,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in musicals like 'Sweeney Todd'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=H. F. Maltby wrote Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street (1936 film).",
            "html": "dbpedia_3514_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What elements contribute to the dark and suspenseful nature of 'Sweeney Todd'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3514_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the success of the film influence later adaptations or interpretations of 'Sweeney Todd'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3514_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a well-known musical composer who might have been involved in creating music for a production of 'Sweeney Todd'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3514_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3514_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3514_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3514_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3514_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3514_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3514_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3514_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3514_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3514_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3514_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe document at file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3514/re-ranker-msmarco/16.txt credits H.F. Maltby as the music writer for \"Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street,\" which is identified as a 1936 film in that document. Therefore, the statement that H. F. Maltby wrote the musical score for Sweeney Todd in the 1936 film version is supported by the information provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "H.F. Maltby is not credited as a writer for the 1936 film \"Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street\". Eric Ansell, not H.F. Maltby, is credited for writing the music in this film.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}